virtualresults.net 2017-11-19

# Privacy Policy - Virtual Results

**Online Privacy**

****We understand the concerns Internet users have about the privacy and security of information. This policy tells you about our priorities for protecting privacy and security of information collected on this website.

**Information Gathered**  
We gather information about website visitors to improve the caliber of online information and services offered. There are two forms of data that we collect on the website: Site Visitorship Data and Personal Information Data. How we collect this information and what we do with it is discussed below.

**Site Visitorship Data**  
We routinely gather data on website activity. This information, “Site Visitorship Data,” is collected on an aggregate basis on public areas of our website, or on an individual basis on the password protected areas of our website that require website visitors to log on using an access code (e.g., userID and/or password). Site Visitorship Data may include information such as (i) how many people visit our website; (ii) the pages they visit and the features they use; (iii) how long they stay on our website; and (iv) the domain name of the Internet website from which visitors are connecting. Site Visitorship Data is generally gathered through the use of cookies and pixel tags.

A “cookie” is a small piece of information that an Internet site sends to a visitor’s computer. In some cases, it is stored on the visitor’s hard drive. Cookies can save the visitor’s name, access codes, screen preferences, the pages of the site viewed by the visitor, and the advertisements viewed or clicked by the visitor. Visitors may decline receipt of the Internet cookie by using the appropriate feature of their Web software, if available. Declining the Internet cookie may, however, interfere with a visitor’s ability to view certain content in our website.

A “pixel tag” is an invisible tag placed on certain pages of our website and is used to track an individual user’s activity on the password protected areas of our website. A pixel tag is also known as a “clear gif.”

**Personal Information Data**  
We collect Personal Information Data such as name, address, phone number, email address, etc. that website visitors provide when they complete any online form, application, survey, or when they initiate a contact request. If you would like to modify any information that you gave us on a form you can do so by completing a new form and submitting it.

We are committed to protecting your personal information. We do not disclose this information to any other third party.

**Collection of Personal Information From Children**  
This website is not directed toward children. We do not knowingly collect or post information from children under the age of eighteen (18). We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate with them in the various interactive activities available on the Internet.

**Email**  
To protect against and to correct misunderstandings, we may monitor electronic communications conducted with us. Further, we may, from time to time, send you marketing messages by email about our products and services. If you do not wish to receive emailed marketing messages from us, use Block Email to add your email address to our database. Note that since this process is automated, we will not respond. If you wish to communicate with us directly, please contact us.

**Hyperlinks**  
This website may contain hyperlinks or “links,” to and from other Internet sites. These sites may have different privacy practices from the one described here. Since this Internet Privacy Policy applies solely to this website, please remember to read the privacy statements of the other Internet sites you visit.

**Security Standards**  
We work hard to ensure that our systems are secure and that they meet industry standards. Where appropriate, we employ firewalls, encryption technology, user access codes (e.g., userIDs and passwords) and other access control mechanisms to control access to systems and data. We continue to assess new technology to evaluate its ability to provide additional protection of personal information we collect on this site.

**Internet Privacy Policy**  
This policy is effective as of September 27, 2004. We reserve the right to change this Internet Privacy Policy at any time. Changes will be effective immediately upon posting to our website. We recommend that visitors to our website re-visit this Internet Privacy Policy on occasion to learn of changes to our privacy practices and policies.

**Contact**  
It is important to us to hear what visitors have to say about our website, our services, or any other issues. If you have any questions and/or concerns, or want to let us know what you think, please contact us.
